《越狱》前情回顾
Previously on Prison Break
老兄  我们不如对半分了 来个双赢?
Listen, why don't I just give you half the money we call it a day?
好吧 你六我四
All right, 60/40.
你个窃贼王八蛋 你最好跪下祈求上帝
You thieving son of a bitch. You better get down on your knees
不要让我找到你
and pray to god that I don't find you.
要是让我找到你 我发毒誓扒你皮抽你筋
Because if I do, mark my words,I'm gonna gut you bow to stern.
- 贝利克先生?  - 什么事?
- Mr. Bellick? - Yeah?
你介意我再问你几个问题吗?
Do you mind answering a few more questions?
我们已经发现布伦斯兄弟
We have a lead as to where burroughs
汇合地点的线索了 是一个他称之为"Bolshoi booze"的地方
will be meeting up with his brother. It's a place he referred to as "Bolshoi Booze".
这是数字
They're numbers.
把经纬坐标输入全球定位系统会发现那是新墨西哥州沙漠中的某处
Plug 'em into your GPS they'll take you to a spot in the New Mexico desert.
爸爸!
- Daddy!
宝贝  准备好出发了吗?
- Hey, baby, you ready to go?
走  快走!
Go, go, go, go, go!
我们接着怎么办?
What do we do now?
她开口了吗?
- she told you anything?
还没有
- Not yet.
那就杀了她
- Then kill her.
但是她知道些事情
- Well, she knows something.
你敢抗命  你就完了!
You disobey me, you are done!
干掉她  Paul!
Put her in the ground, Paul!
只要你告诉我你父亲给了你什么
You're going to die, and all you had to do was
我就放你条生路
tell me what your father gave you.
去死吧
Go to hell.
飞机会停靠在7英里路牌处
The plane's gonna stop at the seven-mile marker,
第四大道  日落时分
route 4 at sunset.
-我们必须出发了  -我带来个人
- We got to go. - I brought someone.
爸爸?
Dad?
我们以前遇到过
We met before.
果然是你
It was you.
别激动  儿子
Go easy, son.
离我远点
Stay away from me.
到底怎么回事?
- What the hell's going on?
我认识他
- I know him.
你说你认识他什么意思? 那根本不可能
What do you mean you know him? That's impossible.
我认识他
I know him.
我了解这个人!
I know this man!
迈克尔...
- Michael...
这就够了
- Maybe that's far enough.
这与你无关
this doesn't concern you.
爸爸  究竟怎么回事?
What the hell's going on, dad?
妈妈死后...
After mom died...
你在少管所
you were in juvie.
他们把我扔给了这个...
They put me with this...
这个养父照管
this foster father
在珀欣大街的家中
down on Pershing avenue.
他打骂我
He punished me,
把我锁起来
locked me up.
如果有人被如此长久地单独关在黑暗之中
If you leave someone alone in the dark for that long,
他的眼睛就会发生变化
their eyes start to adjust.
不管多小的东西都能够看到
You start to see things, no matter how small,
因为如果那些东西存在的话 它们可以帮上忙
because if they exist, they can help you.
助你达成独自关在黑暗中... ...唯一想做的事情
help you do the only thing you want to do...when you're alone in the dark:
逃出去
Get out.
我用过你们见过的所有鱼饵
I've used just about every lure that you could use.
很多种只有专家才能用好
Most of them, you need to be an expert to use.
这款电动鱼饵与众不同
this moto lure's a little different.
每个人 真的是所有人都能用它钓鱼
Everybody, I mean everybody, can fish with it.
而且你还能钓到更大的鱼
And you're gonna catch bigger fish,
钓到更多的鱼
you're gonna catch more fish.
甚至在水草密集处也能起作用
it even works in weedy areas
而通常一般的鱼饵就失灵了
where most top-water lures won't work.
朋友们  看看这个吧
Take a look at this baby.
这玩意看上去像极了小淡水鱼
this thing looks like a real minnow.
这是个非常酷的鱼饵
this is one very cool bait.
我还从未见过这么好的东西
I have never seen anything quite like this.
即便你以前在电视直销上买过鱼饵
even if you've bought lures off of tv in the past
最后失望而归
and been disappointed--
请相信我  我非常清楚你的感受
and believe me, I know how you feel--
对不起  老兄
- Sorry, man.
我以为你出去了
I thought you'd left.
不  我还在这儿
No, still here. Here I am.
是这样的  有些客人
Yeah, it's just that a couple of guests are
投诉你电视开得太响
complaining about the volume of your TV.
对不起  我睡着了
Oh, sorry, I fell asleep.
可能不小心按到遥控器
I must have hit the remote.
我会解决的  谢谢  真对不起
I'll take care of it. Thanks.Sorry. Thanks.
很好  那么请你现在就开轻点
Great.Um, so could you do that for me now, please,
现在就解决掉?
so it's taken care of?
-好的 -谢了
Yeah. Thanks.
好了  开小了
taken care of .
你浴室里没问题吧?
is, uh, everything okay in your bathroom?
你说什么?
Excuse me?
你的浴室  里面声音好大
Your bathroom. There's a noise coming from it.
是啊  我女儿把洗澡视为一种嬉戏
Yeah, my daughter thinks bath time is playtime.
我会清理好的  我保证  抱歉
I will clean it up. Scout's honor.Sorry.
好吧  祝你愉快
All right. Have a nice day.
你也是
Yeah, you, too.
迈克尔  迈克尔  请等等  迈克尔
- Michael, - Michael? - Michael, please wait.
他真的这么对你?
- He did this to you?
迈克尔!  林肯!
- Michael! - Lincoln!
他真的这么对你?
He did this to you?
你怎么可以这么做
How could you do that
对一个活生生的人
to another human being with your own hands?
没事了  你现在安全了
it's okay. You're safe now.
他不会再伤害你了
He's not going to hurt you anymore.
来吧
Come on.
跟我来  不要往回看
Come with me and don't look back.
迈克尔!
Michael!
迈克尔...
Michael...
这一切都会过去的
it's gonna be all right.
莎拉!
Sara!
六个月
Six months
我在那呆了整整六个月
Six months I was in that place.
你那个时候在哪里?
Where were you?
你知道多久了?
How long did you know?
我尽全力最快找到你
I found you as soon as I could.
州政府把你转来转去
The state kept moving you around.
然后你又走了  对吗?
Then you went away again, right?
难道你不知道 我这么离开你心有多痛吗?
You don't think it killed me to leave you like that?
就这样离开
To leave in the first place?
从一开始我就是那个问题的关键
Since the beginning, I was the problem.
从第一天开始
Since day one.
你的人生全是因为我而弄成这样
Your lives are what they are because of me.
林肯告诉了我有关公司的事
Yes, Linc told me about the company.
很明显  你是某种分析家 那就是你不惜放弃家庭而选择的工作
Apparently, you were some kind of analyst.That's the job you chose over your family.
我以为我干的都是对的 我以为我是在保护你
I thought I was doing the right thing. I thought I was protecting you.
爸爸  保护我什么?  防范谁?
From what, dad, from who?
公司有对手! 我对公司非常重要
The company had enemies! I was important to the company.
成了被对付的目标
I became a target.
制约我的最简单的方法就是抓住你!
Easiest way to get to me would be to get to you!
我一知道那有多腐败 我就马上离开了
I left as soon as I realized how corrupt it all was.
- 他们是如何收买政府的... - 你任何时候都可以回来!
-How they were buying the government... - you could have come back at any time!
不  我不能!
- No, I couldn't!
迈克尔  是公司的运作 使我和你们面临这样大的风险
Michael, turning on the company put me and you at even greater risk.
我必须远离是非之地
I had to stay away.
我们曾是你的儿子
We were your sons.
你现在还是  迈克尔
And you still are, Michael.
我们可以收拾这残局
We can fix this.
我回来了这样我们可以应对险境
I came back so that we could fix this.
这冤案永远也不能被澄清
this can never be fixed.
有卷录音带提供了我们所需要的一切
There's a tape.Gives us everything we need.
林肯会被无罪释放
Linc will be set free
如果我们找到录音带的话
if we find it.
你不会相信他觉得那盘录音带在谁手里
You're not gonna believe who he thinks has it.
谁?
Who?
莎拉
sara
是的  身材瘦高  棕色头发  棕色眼睛
Yes, uh, tall and slender,brown hair, brown eyes.
她还严重受伤
She'd be pretty banged up.
急诊室没有符合此描述的人
No one matching that description has been brought into the er.
克里曼
Kellerman.
没有关于沙拉的报告?
No report on Sara Tancredi?
她死了
She's dead.
我正在处理尸体
I'm dealing with the body right now.
你该放心了  都结束了
You must be relieved that it's over.
是的
Yeah
是的  我要挂了
Yeah, I got to go.
还有件事   我要确认
One more thing: Confirmation.
我要你处理尸体前拍张照片给我
I need a photo of the body before disposal.
你用手机拍  然后发给我  我好...
Uh, take one with your phone and send it to me and I'll...
比尔  现在不是时候  好不好?
Bill not a good time right now, all right?
保罗  深呼吸一下  然后去拍张照
Paul, take a breath, then take the picture.
我等着
I'm waiting.
"现在是非常危险的时候
阿维德知道
"Now, Arvid knew that, "
但是他仍然紧紧的抓住龙的绳索
but he held tightly onto the dragon's leash anyway,
怪物拖着小男孩
"as the creature ran into the everdark forest,
跑进了黑暗森林
pulling the young boy behind him."
为什么他不放开绳索呢?
Why didn't he just let go of the leash?
因为他爱他那只龙
Well, because he loved the dragon.
如果你爱谁
Now, when you love someone,
你会绝不会放弃他们
you'll do anything to hold onto them.
会做任何事让他们安全和开心
Anything to keep them safe and happy.
这就是为什么我们在一起露营吗?
Is that why we're camping?
对  我们会永远在一起的
Yep. So we can all be together.
我很开心
I'm happy
我也很开心
I'm happy, too.
拿去吧
Here you go.
现在都解决了  是吧?
Well, it's all working out, huh?
别提了
Don't say that.
此时此刻  在这里
You know, this moment, right here, right now,
一切都是值得的
it's all worth it.
我爱你
I love you
我也爱你
I love you, too.
照片很老了
That's old.
孩子都已经长大了
The kids are bigger now.
对不起  我只是...
Sorry. I was just...
等了太久  是会感到无聊的
getting bored out of your wits'cause you been waiting so long.
我真的很抱歉让你久等
Really sorry about all this.
我们以前这里杀人案不多
We don't get a whole bunch of homicides out here,
现在可能凶手想把以前的补上吧
and, well, we're trying to play catch-up.
请坐
Please, have a seat.
你朋友的事我很遗憾
I'm real sorry about your friend.
病态的世界
Sick world out there.
你说的是真的吗?
Ain't that the truth?
你们俩是一起到堪萨斯州的?
So you guys out here in kansas together?
是的  没错
Yeah. That's right.
来干什么?
Doing what?
嗯...只是来观光
Well, you know, just seeing the sights.
你们离开芝加哥到特比里来观光?
You left Chicago to see the sights in Tribune, Kansas?
上次我说过了  一个人想去哪儿去哪儿
Last time I checked, a man could go where he wanted.
贝利克先生...
Mr. Bellick...
叫我布拉德
Brad.
布拉德  其实我并不关心你们在这里做什么
Brad. I don't really care what you were doing out here.
这只是个程序
We're both in law enforcement.
我们得各闻一口臭屁啊
We can each sniff out a perp like a hot fart.
原谅我的粗话
Pardon my french.
你我都知道你并不是罪犯  所以...
we both know you're not a criminal, so...
我不管你们两个小伙子在这里 是躲着你们的老婆在这里寻开心
I don't care if you boys were out here whoopin' it without your wives or...
或者是"断背"
going brokeback.
什么?  见鬼  不是
What? Hell, no.
我的意思是 我不管你们在这里做什么
My point is, I don't care what you were doing.
我只是要知道当时你们在哪里 还有遇到什么人
I just need to know where you were doing it and who you might have crossed paths with so
然后我就能找到是谁杀死了格雷先生
I can find out who carved up Mr. Geary.
我和加里找到一个福克斯河监狱逃犯的线索
Geary and I got a lead that one of the Fox River Eight
就在这个镇
was in town.
谁?
Which one?
希欧多尔·巴格威尔
Theodore Bagwell.
那个对未成年人犯罪的家伙?
The man who did all those horrible things to those teenagers?
就是他
That's him.
我们想抓住他拿到奖金但是我们没抓住他
We were going to bring him in for the reward money, but we couldn't get a handle on him.
我和格雷意见不和  但是...
Geary and I split up, figured we didn't have a shot, but...
-但是什么? -在这发生以后
but what? -Well, after what happened,
我开始想加里可能遇到了帝博格
I'm starting to think maybe Geary ran into ol' Bagwell after all.
在特比里镇?
Right here in tribune?
布拉德  你觉得你能回答我几个问题
Now, Brad, do you think you could answer some questions
帮助我们追踪到希欧多尔  博格威尔吗?
that might help us track Theodore Bagwell?
我会很感激的
I'd be indebted.
我会尽我所能帮你抓住那个狗娘养的
I'll do whatever I can to help you nail that son of a bitch.
你认为录音带在莎拉那里?
You think Sara has this tape?
不  政府这样认为
Government does.
我昨天还见过她
I just saw her yesterday.
她自己都不知道她有那东西
If she does have anything, she doesn't know.
她现在在哪儿?
Well, where is she now?
我不知道
I don't know.
有什么办法可以联系到她?
Any way you can get in touch with her?
买个手机  我打电话给他
We brought cell phones.I could call her.
拜托  拜托  老兄
Please, please, please, bro,
到巴拿马再打电话给她
call her from Panama.
我们只有不到两个小时了
We got less than two hours.
我要赶上飞机
I got to make the flight.
什么?
What?
快跑
Run!
快跑!
你刚才说的那辆车在哪儿?
where's this car you keep talking about?
就在山后面
- It's over the ridge.
把枪给我
- Give me that.
你们去开车!
You guys head for the car!
快!
Go!
快!  走!
Come on! Go!
回去接他!
Go back for him!
爸!
Dad!
走!
Go!
成功了!  狗娘养的!
Son of a bitch! We made it!
成功了!
We made it!
林肯
Linc.
苏克雷  带我们去医院
Sucre, get us to a hospital.
这儿? 见鬼  我还要去找...
Out here? Where the hell am I going to find...?
带我们去医院  求你!
Just get us to a hospital, please!
好吧
Okay.
别担心  你会没事的
Don't worry. You're going to make it.
这是胆汁  他把我打穿了
It's bile. He got me clean through.
你会没事的...坚持住
You're going to be okay! Just... hold on.
你们两个  听我说
Listen to me, both of you.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我希望我从未离开过你们
I wish I had never left.
别说话  别说话  呼吸
Don't talk, don't talk. Just breathe.
好了  你想要一个香蕉花生酱三明治吗?
Okay, so do you want a pb & b?
不要
Not really.
我肚子痛
My tummy hurts.
她的背包呢?
Where's her knapsack?
她的什么?
Her what?
她的背包  她的药在里面
Knapsack. Her medicine's in it.
我不知道  我刚才抱起她就跑
I don't know, baby. I just grabbed her and ran.
她需要吃药
She needs that medicine.
两天不吃就不行
She can't go two days without it.
是的  我知道
Yeah, I know.
我是她爸爸  好吗?
I'm her father, all right?
在哪儿?
Where is it?
宝贝  冷静点  你在找什么?
Baby.Baby, look. Calm down.What are you looking for?
告诉我是什么  我能帮你找  好吗?
Just tell me what it is, and I'll go ahead and get it, okay?
她的处方
Her prescription.
是个备份
It's a backup.
保险起见我另外保留了一个
I keep an extra, in case.
好的
Okay.
我们只要去药店买就行
so all we need to do is find a pharmacy.
别担心
Don't worry.
嘿   看起来我们要去兜一圈 小宝贝
Hey, looks like we're going on a ride, sweet pea.
我们绑住了帝博格 他可能拿了加里的东西
Look, we nail Bagwell, he might still have some of Geary's things on him,
比如背包  他有些私人物品在里面
like his backpack,which has his personal stuff in it.
他妻子喜欢的东西
I know his wife would love to have it.
如果我们找到博格威尔 你可以私下交给她
If we find Bagwell, you can give it to her personally.
-谢谢 -这也是我仅仅能做的
Thanks. -It's the least I can do considering ho you're helping me out.
因为你帮了我很多 虽然有人还在担心...
Though some of the guys on the force are concerned about...
他们担心什么?
what are they concerned about?
没什么 只是你知道
Nothing.But you know what?
为什么你没有告诉我所有的事情?
Why don't you tell me what you know, we'll get Geary's effects back to his family,
我们能抓住博格威尔  拿回加里的家庭财产
we'll track down Bagwell,
我敢肯定所有人与此有关的人都会知道 你对我们的帮助十分宝贵
I'll make sure that everybody involved knows that your help was invaluable.
我还是劝你说出大部分
I'll even recommend that you get most of,
那笔悬赏金
if not all of, that reward money.
那到底
What is it exactly
警方的人在怀疑些什么?
that the guys
on the force were concerned about?
他们有人认为 你头上的伤还有疑点
Well, some of them thought that you weren't being totally upfront about your head injury.
我是说  实际上这的确有点反常
I mean, to be fair, it does seem a little off
你会没看见从前面 袭击你正脑门儿的人
that you didn't see the guy who hit you smack-dab on the forehead.
你厉害
You got me.
盖瑞和我
Geary and me
对于怎么去找到博格威尔起了点分歧
had a little dustup over how to go about finding Bagwell.
然后我们动起手来  他打了我
It got physical, and he hit me.
我们俩打架就好象兄弟间那种
The two of us, we fought like brothers.
我不想到警察面前去告他一状
I didn't want to rat him out to the cops.
打完后  我们分开了
After the fight, we split up.
之后...
And then...
你知道之后他发生了什么...
Well, you know what happened to him.
我真希望当初我们没打架  你明白吗?
I just wish to hell we'd never fought, you know?
也许他现在就还活着...
Maybe then he'd still be...
布拉德  你不能这么责怪自己
Brad, you can't blame yourself.
我们为什么不将悲痛化为力量
Why don't we refocus our energy on
来找那个杀了你朋友的人?
finding the man who killed your friend?
罗伊也一定这么想
That's what Roy would've wanted.
好了吧  宝贝儿
All right, baby.
有保险吗?
Insurance card?
没  我没有保险
Uh, no, I don't have insurance.
你开消炎药不用保险?
You're paying for dexamethasone without insurance?
有医疗补贴补助什么的吗?
You got medicaid, medicare or something?
没有
Nope.
我用现金付就好了
Um, I'll just pay cash.
一共125块
It's $125.
(仍然在逃的罪犯及家人)
请问?
Excuse me?
好了吗?
哦  对不起
Um, oh, sorry.
很抱歉我没零钱了
Sorry I don't have anything smaller.
我到后面去把这100块换开
I have to go to the back to get change for $100.
马上就回来
So... I'll be right back.
就在那儿! 医院!
- Right there! Hospital!
我看见了  我看见了
- I see it. I see it.
快带我们过去
Just get us there.
不  你们会被抓的
No, you'll be caught.
那就被抓吧
Then we'll be caught.
我不会让你死的
I'm not gonna let you die.
那就听我的
Then listen to me.
去找莎拉 唐克雷蒂
You find Sara Tancredi.
她能终结这一切
She can end this.
都看你的了
It's up to you now.
通缉一辆深蓝色小轿车
yeah, I want an alarm out on a dark blue Sedan.
车牌AE9268.
License: AE9268.
洛斯克鲁斯东南40英里处
40 miles southeast of Los Cruces.
现在就去办
Do it now.
该死的!
oh, come on!
什么事?
What?
哪家医院?
What hospital?
医生就报警了 就在里面
Docs called us in,He's in here.
我们查了他的名字
We ran his name.
结果查到他正受到两项走私毒品的通缉
Came back with two federal drug smuggling warrants out on him.
听说你想和我谈谈
Heard you wanted to talk to me.
我有些你们感兴趣的信息...
I got some information the feds want...
有关迈克尔 斯科菲尔德的
about Michael Scofield.
比如他会在哪儿搭飞机
Like where he's catching a ride.
会在哪儿?
And where would that be?
不只是地点还有时间
It's not just the where but the when.
而且时间就快到了
That when is coming up soon.
但我想先谈谈条件
But I want to cut a deal first.
给我点时间
Give us a minute.
你还有什么想说的？
Anything you want to say?
一天
One day.
我们只有这些了
That's all we had.
在那几天里
Back then,
情况最惨的时候...
when things were at their worst...
有那么几天我以为
there were days I thought
我再也见不到阳光了
I'd never see the sun again.
但他救了我一命
But he saved my life.
我只希望他能把我们当作他生活的一部分
I just wish he could have let us be a part of his.
是啊
Yeah.
我会告诉他的  好的
I'll tell him.
这是开给你的条件
Here's the deal.
所有指控都被撤消并且政府
All charges dropped and the government
会负责你的医疗费用直到你被驱逐出境
picks up medical costs until you're fit to be deported,
只要你提供正确的信息
all contingent upon your information being accurate.
斯科菲尔德在哪儿?
Where's Scofield?
不要驱逐出境
No deportation.
我要美国公民身份
I want citizenship.
公民身份?
Citizenship?
做为和你们合作的动机  而且我要书面的
A little incentive, and I want it in writing.
我不想再和你玩下去了
I'm so tired of playing games.
那么开始打字吧
Well, start typing.
没有外接起博器
No external pacemaker.
这个不错...没有吗啡滴液
Oh, this is a good one-- no morphine drip.
-你在做什么?  -FBI 出去出去
What are you doing? FBI. Out. Out!
出去出去！
Out. Out!
你他妈做什么?
What the hell are you doing?
给你点合作的动机啊
Giving you a little incentive.
别!
Come on!
别这样  你个狗娘...
Come on, you son of A...
他们什么也没找到?
And they found nothing?
好的谢了
Okay, thanks.
你的直觉真强啊  布拉德
Well, your instincts are great, Brad,
管区警察今天是派了人到郝兰德的家里去了
but the precinct actually sent a unit over to Hollander's house today.
一个匿名报警电话声称有人闯入
An anonymous caller said they saw an intruder
但里面没人
but no one was there.
该死的
Damn it.
如果你知道博格威尔和郝兰德的事
If you knew about Bagwell and Hollander,
为什么你们不到那里去(找他)呢?
why didn't you just head over there yourself?
我们找不到那地方
We couldn't find the house.
是吗?
Really?
电话簿里有啊
It's listed.
失陪一下
excuse me.
谢谢
Thank you.
一切都好吗?
Everything okay?
是啊一切都好
Yeah, yeah, everything's fine.
布拉德  你曾经去过冯特洛利酒店吗?
Brad, have you ever been to the Fauntleroy hotel?
-大概离这里15分钟的路 -从来没听说过
It's about 15 minutes from here.-Never heard of it.
那就奇怪了  他们找到
Well, that's strange,'cause they found
这张收据  就在盖伊的房间里
this receipt in Geary's hotel room.
是用你的信用卡结的
It's from your credit card.
我不知道怎么会跑那里去的
I don't know how that got there.
我觉得你是在回避这个问题
I think you're being evasive.
你应该跟我说实话  贝利克先生
You should tell me the truth, Mr.Bellick.
怎么不叫我布拉德了?
What happened to "Brad"?
大概7年前我办了第一起
About seven years ago, I got my first
凶杀案--一个漂亮的女子
homicide case   a woman, pretty.
被粗暴的袭击
She was brutally attacked.
她那兽性的男友留着她等死
Animal boyfriend left her for dead,
但她还有口气...勉强的
but she was still breathing... barely.
她在她的手机上输入了
But she punched into her cell phone
凶手的号码  结果她就帮我们破了案
the killer's number,so she solved the crime for us.
当我们找到那收据的时候  布拉德
When we found the receipt, Brad,
盖瑞的手  他的手指着你的名字
it was in Geary's hand, his finger pointing to your name.
他用生前最后一点力气告诉我们你杀了他
With his last ounce of strength, he told us you killed him.
好吧  听着
Okay, listen.
盖瑞和我在郝兰德家里发现了博格威尔
Geary and I found Bagwell at Hollander's house.
我们逼问了他
We roughed him up
直到他告诉我们
till he told us
他从犹它挖来的那500万的下落
here he'd hid the five million bucks we knew he dug up in utah.
等我们找到那笔钱后格雷耍了我
When we found the money,Geary double-crossed me.
他把我打晕并拿走了钱
He hit me in the head and took the cash.
我和格雷的死没关系
I had nothing to do with Geary's death.
你听见我说的了吗?
You hear what I'm saying?
我才是受害者  不是那个狗娘养的!
I'm the victim here,not that son of a bitch!
快点  快点  快点
Come on, come on, come on.
还没好吗  宝贝儿?
Where are you at, baby?.
你能快点吗?
Hey, uh, could you hurry it up?
已经晚了  我得快点回家
It's just it's getting really late-- I got to get home.
给你
And, um,
这是20块
that's $20,
40  50
$40, $50,
加20是70
and $20 is $70.
1块2块3块
One, two, three,
4...
four,
5... 一共75
five...... seventy-five.
没搞错吧
You got to be kidding me.
女士
Ma'am.
下午好啊  警官
Afternoon, officer.
你带着身份证吗?
Do you have any id with you?
没 我就随便走过来的
no.I walked over here,
什么也没带
so i didn't carry anything with me.
是吗?  你从哪儿走过来的?
Did you? Where'd you walk from?
有什么问题吗  警官?
Is there a problem, officer?
除非是你自找问题  富兰克林太太
There's only a problem if you make one, Ms. Franklin.
你打算告诉我们你丈夫在哪儿吗?
You want to tell us where your husband is?
我不知道
I don't know.
请把双手放在背后  女士
Place your hands behind your back, please, ma'am.
真对不起  宝贝
Baby, I'm so sorry.
上帝啊
Oh, my god.
妈妈在哪儿?
Where's mommy?
妈妈嘛...妈妈要晚点再和我们碰面了
Mommy, uh, mommy is going to meet us later.
好吗?
Okay?
我是
- Yes.
照片在哪?
- Where's the photo?
比尔  这是一个战术的失误
Bill, there was a tactical error.
别跟我说那些
I don't want
从手册上面学来的术语
terminology from the cover your ass handbook, Paul.
发生了什么?
What happened?
情况有些特殊
There were unforeseen circumstances,
事情不是像我们想象的那么顺利
things that could not be predicted.
莎拉在哪?
Where's Sara?
你是不是让她跑了?
She's gone, isn't she?
是的  让她跑了
Yes, she got away,
但我不会让她...
but there's no way that she could...
比尔
Bill.
我不会让你就这么死的
I'm not going to let you die.
我是爱你的
I love you.
你知道的  是吗?
You know that, don't you?
太多了
Too many.
因为我想让你自由死了太多的人
Too many people died because I wanted you to be free.
这是无法预料的事情
You couldn't have known, Michael.
迈克尔
Michael.
我们也不知道...
You couldn't have know it...
结果会是这样
would have ended up like this.
但这是现实
But it did.
他们要抓住他
They wanted him.
他们要他死
They wanted him in the ground,
现在他们如愿了
and they got their wish.
这件事情不会就这样结束的 迈克尔
this thing is not going to end here, Michael.
我知道
- I know.
被牵连的人会越来越多
- It's going to keep spreading.
他们的手沾染了太多的血
Their hands are going to get more and more bloody.
是啊  但问题是
Well, the question is,
是他们的手沾满了鲜血  还是我们的?
is the blood on their hands... or ours?
兄弟们  真遗憾
I'm sorry, guys.
但  我们得走了
We got to go.
快到达拉斯的国界线那里去巡逻
Get back on with Border Patrol.
通知达拉斯海军预备队的飞机场
Call the Navy Reserve Air Station in Dallas.
让他们的飞机进入警戒状态
They've got planes on alert.
我们要拦截一架  白色的单引擎飞机
We need an intercept of a white, single engine
号码为A-36  它正驶向国界线
a-36 beech heading toward the border.
通知墨西哥那边疏散准备开始国际追捕
Call Mexico, get clearance for an international pursuit.
告诉他们如果他们需要把飞机打下来  没问题
Tell them if they got to take the plane down, just do it.
伙计们快上来!
Come on, guys!
快上来啊
Guys, come on.
快点啊
Come on, guys.
怎么了?
What?
我们要留下来
We're staying.
(西班牙语)
迈克尔 我们等了那么久不就是等这一天吗
Michael, this is what we've been waiting for.
也许  我们有一天会去拜访你的
Maybe we'll see you down there somewhere.
这次我不能说服你了  对吗?
I can't talk you out of this one, can i?
好吧  希望还能见到你们
Well I hope so
保重
Be good.
迈克尔谢谢你
Thank you, Michael.
谢谢你为我做的一切
Thank you for everything.
保重
- Take care, all right?
我会的
- I will.
兄弟  一路顺风
Fly safe, papi.
给他们点颜色
Give 'em hell.
到了巴拿马一切都会好起来的
Panama would've been good.
你准备好了吗?
Are you ready for this?
都等了好几年了
- Been waiting years.
很好
- Good to hear it.
因为现在开始我们要转守为攻了
'Cause today is the day we stop running.
现在怎么做?
- What now?
我们先回车里去
- We go back to the car.
到一个边界线上的城市
I drive to a border town,
找到有电话信号的地方
find a cell phone signal.
给莎拉打电话
Call Sara.
妈的我叫的那些飞机都去哪了?!
Where the hell are those jets?
你听到了吗?
you hear that?
是的
Yeah.
靠边停车
Pull over.
哦  天啊他们紧跟在  苏克雷的后面
oh, god, they're going after Sucre.
他们要把他抓住
They're gonna take him down.
他们是怎么知道的?
- How'd they find out?
不知道
- I don't know.
迈克尔
Michael.
我想知道现在到底进展的怎么样了
I want to know what the hell's going on.
如果你要拘留我  现在时间也差不多到了
If you could've arrested me,you would've already done it.
我要走了
I'm out of here.
贝利克先生  现在由不得你来选择
Not really an option for you, Mr. Bellick.
你凭什么这么说  你有证据吗? 他把它落在口袋里了
What do you got, a receipt? He left it in his pocket.
只是打了一架?  有什么了不起的
A fight? Big deal.
我在芝加哥有十个好兄弟  他们都知道格雷和我
I got ten pals in Chicago tell you and I
每隔一个月就打一次
threw down once a month.
你说的对
You're right.
他们手中的证据还不够
Any of those things on their own,
还不至于给你定罪
probably not enough.
但是如果加上这个...
But when you add this...
这是什么鬼东西?
what the hell's that?
是你给格雷先生的留言
You left a message for Mr. Geary.
你个窃贼王八蛋  竟然敢偷我的东西
You thieving son of a bitch,
你最好跪下来乞求上帝  让我不要找到你
you better get down on your knees and pray to god that I don't find you.
如果让我找到你
Because if I do, mark my words:
我发毒誓扒你皮抽你筋
I'm gonna gut you bow to stern.
你想再听一次吗?
You want to hear it again?
在这种情况下
Now at this juncture, Brad,
我想如果你坦白交代的话 相信你会得到宽大处理的
things will go a whole lot easier for you if you admit to the crime.
你给我听着  你这个狡猾的婊子
you manipulative little bitch
罗伊 格雷不是我杀死的!
Now you listen to me,I did not kill Roy Geary!
你听清楚我跟你说的没有!
You understand what I'm telling you!
是  博格威尔陷害我的!
Bagwell set me up!
把你的手给我拿开!
Get your hds off of me!
布拉德  贝利克你被逮捕了
Bradley Bellick, you are under arrest
因为你谋杀了  罗伊 威廉 格雷
for the first-degree murder of Roy William Geary.
你有权保持沉默
You have a right to remain silent.
你所说的一切  都可能作为指控你的不利证据
Anything you say can be used against you in a court of law.
你有权请律师在你受审时到场
You have a right to talk with an attorney and to have him present with you when being questioned.
如果你请不起律师...
If you cannot hire an attorney...
这里是总统 莱娜斯的办公室
President reynolds' office.
我是  保罗 克里曼特工
this is agent Paul Kellerman.
我需要马上和总统通话
I need to speak with the president right now, please.
很抱歉  这个部门没有克里曼特工
I'm sorry, this administration isn't familiar with an agent Kellerman.
简  是我
June, it's me.
我要和凯若琳通话  快
I need to speak with Caroline now.
简  如果你不给我接通的话
June, if you don't put me through,
我一定会让总统知道 是你不让我给她提供重要情报的
I'll make certain that the  president knows thatyou were the one
who did not allow me to provide her with some very important information.
快
Now.
很抱歉
I'm sorry,
这个部门没有克里曼特工...
this administration
isn't familiar with an agent...
请您在  滴  一声之后留言
Please leave a message after the tone.
比尔别这样
Bill, don't do this.
我把我的一生都献给了这个国家和你  凯若琳
I've dedicated my life to this country, to Caroline.
我把我的一切都奉献了
Everything I have, I give.
把每张图片  每份资料
Every photo, every file.
全部删除
Get rid of it all.
让他成为无名鬼
Make him a ghost.
我曾是一名出色的军人
I've been a perfect soldier.
我从来都没向你索取什么  从来没有
I've never asked   anything of you, ever.
但是现在我只希望
But I'm asking now.
比尔别这么做
Bill, don't do this.
我看不见他了
I don't see him.
相信我
Trust me,
我们还没有摆脱他
we haven't lost him yet.
林肯?
Linc?
把车停下
- Stop the car.
什么?
- What?
我们应该把车停下
We got to stop the car.
这里有一个无线电塔
That's a radio tower over there.
我们一定能接通信号的
It must be picking up some kind of analog signal.
如果我们靠近它的话
We got to get closer.
把车调过来
Turn around.
如果他追上来怎么办?
What about your  friend back there?
都到这个地步了
If we're gonna go down,
管不了这么多了
might as well go down swinging.
快点  快点  快点...
Come on, come on, come on...
连接成功了
we are in business.
已经打通了
it's going through.
快点 莎拉  快接电话
Come on, Sara, pick up.
莎拉
Sara?
喂  喂  迈克尔? 迈克尔?
Hello? Hello? Michael? Michael?